ジャーン
その反応でよろしい
や 夜ト
ここにあやかしがいます
嫌悪や恐怖は境界を引きやすい
Ta-da!
Here we have a Phantom!
境界
神器が唯一使える矛であり 盾
Y-Yato?!
それが境界だ
Good. That reaction will do just fine!
お前 この間もいい仕事して見せたからな
It's easier to draw borderlines with hate and fear.
そろそろ教えとく
Borderlines?
ほ 褒めても何も出ねぇし
A borderline serves as a
Regalia's shield and only weapon.
まず 指を矛の形にして
You did pretty well the other day, so I think you're ready to learn how to make one.
あやかしと自分との間に
一線を引いてみろ
F-Flattery won't get you anywhere.
First, put your middle and index fingers together like this,
い…一線
then try drawing a line between you and the Phantom.
すっごい これが境界ですか
O-Okay.
ああ 己と他と分かつ一線だ
A...
あやかしはそれを超えることはできない
line!
夜トもこれ出来るんですか
Wow!
あ 私は
This is a borderline?!
Yup. It's basically a barrier
that Regalia can create.
お前も俺も無理だ
境界は神器だけの力
Phantoms can't pass through it.
神器なら誰でもできるが
Can you do this too?
初めからここまで強く隔てられるとは
C-Can I?!
You and I can't.
俺が知る神器の中でも 初めてだ
The ability to create borderlines is a Regalia power.
Any Regalia can make them,
夜トが知る神器
but creating one this strong on the first try?
Out of all the Regalia I know, this is the first time I've seen something like this.
あの　夜トが野良と呼んでいた方も神器なんですよね
All the Regalia he knows...
あいつか
あいつは
Um, that girl you called
"Nora" is a Regalia too, right?
都合がいい女なんだよ
えっ
Oh, her?
She's...
a friend with benefits.
Huh?
弾丸込めた小銃を　僕は片手に持っている
Noragami
震えた君のいる場所へ　足を早め向かっている
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
焦る心を急かしただけ
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
留まる気配もなく　進んでいく
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
終わりと始まりの境目
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
全て重なった
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
閉口して　僕は待っていた
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
ドアを蹴破る　その音を
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
閉口して　僕は待っていた
I was waiting helplessly
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
閉口して　僕は待っていた
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
閉口して　僕は待っていた
I was there waiting helplessly
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
閉口して　僕は待っていた
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
もう怖れることはないよ
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
固く閉ざされたドアを蹴破った
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
吸い付いた銃口が跳ねて
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
昨日の僕を貫いた
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dan
gan
ko
me
ta
sho
u
ju
wo
mo
明日への僕は歩き始めた
tte
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
明日への僕は歩き始めた
ka
ta
明日への僕は歩き始めた
ku
to
za
sa
re
ta
do
a
wo
ke
ya
bu
tta
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
su
i
tsu
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
i
ta
ju
u
ko
ga
ha
ne
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
ki
no
u
bo
ku
wo
tsu
ra
nu
i
ta
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
I accept the lingering despair
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
ma
ta
ko
n'
ya
ma
chi
a
wa
se
you
Let's meet again tonight
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于任何商业用途
日听:小然&千夜  翻译:maki&迩祢  校对:木落&叶隐  时间轴:久嘉  压制:久嘉
I'm going to look after Yukine-kun!
雪音君の面倒は私が見ます
Huh?
えっ
What are you talking about?
お前 何言って
ひよりのとこなんて ダメに決まってんだろ
There's no way you could handle him.
No, there's no way you can handle him.
一番行っちゃだめなのは夜トのところです
You don't even have a place to live or anything close to a stable life!
ただでさえ お家もなく ちゃんとした生活が送れてないのに
What with your ex-girlfriends, your affairs, and your friends with benefits!
やれ元カノだの
不倫だの
都合のよい人だの
Your depravity knows no end!
次から次へと 不純すぎます
保護者失格です
You're unfit to be his guardian!
雪音君は私の家で預かるのが一番です
Yukine-kun's better off staying with me!
Get away from her!
は～な～れ～ろ
ちょっと 何するんですか
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
いや めっちゃ刺されてるから
I'm tingling all over the place!
Get your clammy hands off of him!
その湿気た手を放してください
Can't you see he doesn't like it?!
雪音君嫌がってんじゃないですか
Just look! I'm getting all tingly! Really tingly!
だっちゅう ほら きてるきてる
きてきて きてるから
Sheesh!
もう 何なんですか 一体
What's your problem?!
I already told you!
だから こいつが良からぬことを考えると
Whenever an indecent thought pops into his head, I end up in a world of pain!
俺が痛い目に遭うんだってば
良からぬこと
Indecent?
Oh, come on!
ああ もう
A boy and a girl living in the same house?!
男女が一つ屋根の下で暮らすなんてな
Yukine's guaranteed to have
dirty thoughts in that situation!
雪音にやましい考えが生まれまくるに決まってんだろ
That's why he absolutely cannot stay with you!
だから絶対にダメなの
エッチーのはどこどのジャージーの人でしょう
We all know the one with dirty thoughts here is a certain someone in sweats.
雪音くんはいい子ですよ
Yukine-kun's a good boy.
There's nothing to worry about!
何も心配ありません
おいで 雪音くん
Come with me, Yukine-kun!
行くな 雪音
Don't do it, Yukine!
Chapter 5
Borderline
でっけー家
Your house is huge.
Do you come from a
super rich family or something?
ひよりってお嬢様なの
Don't be silly.
何言ってるの
ただの中学生だよ
I'm just an ordinary middle schooler.
只事ではないと思うけど
This doesn't seem very "ordinary" to me.
Hey, where are your parents?
そういゃ ひよりの親は
Lucky for us...
それがね 今日はちょうど帰りが遅いの
They'll be coming home late tonight.
Huh?! Y-You mean it's just you and m—
そ それって 二人っきりってこと
Yukine! Shush!
雪音くん シー
お帰りなさい ひよりちゃん
Welcome home, Hiyori-chan.
S-Sasaki-san.
さ 佐々木さん
ただいま
I'm back.
お風呂沸かしときましたから
I've prepared the bath.
良かったら入ってくださいね
You can use it whenever you're ready.
Whoa! Awesome!
すっげー
雪音君はこの部屋自由に使って
Feel free to use this room, Yukine-kun.
Huh? Are you sure?
いいの
Isn't this your room?
ひよりの部屋なんじゃ
No, it's my brother's.
ううん お兄ちゃんの
Brother?
お兄ちゃん
年の離れた兄なの
He's a lot older than me.
でも今は使ってないから 大丈夫だよ
But he doesn't live here anymore, so don't worry about it.
そっか
Huh...
ひより 兄貴いんだ
I didn't know you had a big brother.
私の部屋は隣だから
My room's right next door,
so let me know if you need anything.
何かあったら言って
Well, see you in a bit!
じゃ また後でね
Okay.
うん
Hiyori sure has it good.
ひよりって ホント恵まれてんな
計画通りです
Just as planned!
It looks like nobody's gonna notice!
Not our housekeeper nor my parents!
この調子なら
お手伝いの佐々木さんにも両親にもバレずに
Oh! Welcome—
あっ　お帰
We're home!
ただいま
We picked up a cake, Hiyori!
ひとり ケーキ買ってきたわよ
ママ 仕事終わりの一杯 飲んでいい
Mind if I have an after-work drink, honey?
もう しょうがないわね
Well, if you must!
このために生きてる
Now this is what I love for!
Now for some snacks.
Wait, Dear.
おつまみ　おつまみ
ちょっとあなた 手は洗いまし
Have you washed your...
あなた
Dear!
You should know better than to
grab whatever you want like that!
つまみ食いなんてして みっともない
ついね ね ほら つい
Oh, I couldn't help myself.
Your mom's pretty sharp.
日和の母ちゃん 鋭いな
What are you doing here?!
一体何しに来たんですか
なんだよ
Gimme a break.
What's the harm if they don't notice me?
バレなきゃ 俺だっていてもいいだろう
It ruins the whole point of me looking after Yukine-kun!
それじゃ 雪音君を預かった意味がありません
ひより あいつどうしてる
Hiyori.
How's he feel about this?
そりゃ 喜んでますよ
He's delighted, of course.
Now he doesn't have to sleep in
the first shrine he finds, unlike you.
夜トみたいに そこらの神社で寝泊まりするわけじゃありませんし
この家とは違って 境内や祠は神域だ
Unlike this house, shrine grounds and their buildings are sacred territory.
They keep us safe from Phantom attacks.
そこなら あやかしに襲われずに済む
Even so...
ですが
夜は闇に巣食うあやかしが動き出す
The night is when the Phantoms
that lurk in the darkness come out.
It's a time of devilry.
魔が産まれる時間だ
I don't think he'll be able to handle it.
特に あいつは耐えられねーだろうけどな
Huh?
You see, Yukine...
雪音は
あいつは
He's...
afraid of the dark.
闇を怖がってる
あったかい風呂とかすっげー久しぶりだ
It's been, like, forever since I last had a warm bath.
I wonder what he'll do
if I don't go back to him.
あいつ
このまま俺が傍にいなかったら どうすんだろ
Yuki
あの女の子 使ったりすんのかな
Will he use that girl or something?
そしたら 俺って
Then what'll happen to me?
Huh?
あれ この匂いどっかで
Why does this smell seem familiar?
もしかして これって
Wait, don't tell me...
Hi-Hiyo... Hiyo...
ひ ひよ ひよ ひよ ひよひよ ひよりの入った後の風呂
Did Hiyori use this bath right before me?!
おお　ここに忘れてたか
Oh!
Guess I forgot to grab it after my bath!
Hey, Hiyori!
おい ひより
早く次風呂入りなさい
I'm done with the bath now! It's your turn!
Gotta build... strong quads...
大腿四頭筋を 鍛えねば
Yukine-kun?
雪音君
Sorry to wake you.
起してわりぃ
Not at all. What's the matter?
ううん　どうしたの
Your dad turned off the
lights in my room just now.
さっき俺の部屋の明かり ひよりの親父に消されたんだよ
I'm, like, not comfortable in the dark, so...
なんか暗いとさ 落ち着かなくて
Oh...
まあ そっか
I see.
Want to sleep with me, then?
じゃあ 一緒に寝る
Huh?!
It's okay with me. Come in!
いいよ おいで
N-No, I can't...
そ そそ そんな
Hurry up, now. It's getting cold.
早く 寒いから
B-But...
で で でで でも
誰かと一緒に寝るのって 久しぶり
I can't remember the last time I slept with someone like this!
Oh...
Yukine-kun...
雪音君も いい匂い
You smell nice, too.
あたしね この匂い 好きなの
I like this smell.
It feels nice being next to you.
そばにいると 心地いい
Oh, Yukine-kun?
ゆ～き～ねくん
The hell are you doing here?!
お前 な 何でここに
Don't give me that, you little perv!
何でじゃねーよ このエロガキ
What were you about to do?!
お前 何しようとした
I didn't...
違う
H-Hiyori invited me into her bed!
あっ　あれはひよりが呼んだから
お前に女は早ぇっつんだよ
You aren't ready for girls yet.
Focus on this dreamboat for now.
今はオレ様だけにしとけ
You're grossing me out, you sweats-wearing sicko.
何キモい事言ってんだ ジャージー野郎
What...
お前だっているじゃん
You have a girl too!
俺と同じ神器の子
Another Regalia, just like me!
俺がいなくたって
It's not like you need me.
今夜も時化出やがる
Gonna be another stormy night.
東角 0.9 0.7
Distance to downtown: 0.9.
0.7.
六時の方向 来ます
Incoming, on your six!
行くぞ
Let's go.
Noragami
付き合ってくれてありがとうねぇ
Thanks for coming along with me!
Yeah. Nothing else to do anyway.
うん　ほかにやることねえし
Do you want those?
それほしいの
Uh, no...
いや
It's starting to get cold out, after all.
これから寒くなるもんね
Let's see how much I have...
あるかな
No, really! It's fine!
ちょ　いいよ
I don't need anything!
別に何もいらねえって
No, no, let me help you out!
ううん　このくらい任せて
Really, I'm okay!
本当いいって
I mean, no one can see me,
ほら　俺人に見えてねえし
so I can always borrow stuff if I really need to!
いざとなったら　ちょこっと借りちゃえばさ
Huh?
なぁ
See?
Y-You know better than that, Yukine-kun!
だめだよ　雪音君
That's no different from stealing!
それじゃ泥棒と一緒だよ
Huh? Hey, I'm only borrowing it.
いや　借りただけだって
I'll give it right back—
すぐ返すし
It's still wrong.
でもだめ
Give it here.
ほら　貸して
何かほしいものがある時は相談して
If you ever want something, just tell me.
Okay?
ねぇ
Yukine-kun?
雪音君
Hey.
おい
Fun Friend Park
夜ト　何してるんですか
Yato?! What are you doing?!
Just trying to relax a little!
I was feeling kinda stressed.
気分悪いから　休憩中
You are looking after him, I hope.
ちゃんとあいつの面倒見てんだろうな
Sounds like he's up to no good again.
また何かやったみてえだけど
How did you know that?
な　何で夜トに分かって
I keep telling you.
言ってるだろ　主と神器は一心同体
Master and Regalia share mind and body.
I can feel it every time
Yukine gives in to temptation!
雪音に魔が差せば　俺がざくっとさされるの
そういう風にできたんだ 主と神器って
That's just how it works between Regalia and their masters.
それじゃ　お父様の酒を盗んだ夜トも同じで
Then, does that mean Yukine-kun also felt it
when you swiped some of my father's drinks?
雪音君も刺されてるんじゃ
Nope.
それはない
The pain from immoral thoughts only goes in one direction:
精神の乱れによる苦痛は
神器から主にのみ
from Regalia to Master.
一方通行でしかないからな
All Regalia used to be people.
神器は　本は人間だ
人間は罪を犯す
And people sin.
恨み　恐れ　妬み　焦り　悲しみ　欲望
Resentment, fear, envy,
desperation, sadness, greed...
Used Games
Super Bargain
!!
Special Sale
Unbeatable Price
Limited Time Only
上げたらきりがないが　それらに魔は差す
Temptation is born from these emotions.
その罪は苦痛となり
The sin of acting on that temptation turns to pain, which is how we learn through our Regalia
神器を通して　俺たちは学ぶ
what is right and wrong.
善と悪を
いいか　ひより
Listen, Hiyori.
You seem to have to wrong idea, so let me set things straight.
勘違いしているようだから　言っておく
People decide for themselves what's right and wrong, but those standards don't apply to gods.
善悪は人が決めるが
神そのものにそれらはないんだ
つまり神様はねぇ　何をしてもいいんだよ
In other words...
gods can do whatever they want.
Including hurting someone... or taking their life.
何者を傷つけようが　殺めようがな
Huh?
いずれ雪音にも仕置きをしてやる
Someday, I'll give Yukine his punishment too.
神の裁きをな
Divine punishment.
Yato...
夜ト
He once killed a Regalia.
神器を斬ったことがあるの
人斬りもするんだよ
He kills people too.
I-I'm...
わ　私　雪音君を探してきます
going to look for Yukine-kun now!
ったく　でっかいおとしもんして
Man...
Talk about forgetting something important.
ひより　まだ怒ってかな
I wonder if Hiyori's still mad at me.
やばっ　もうこんな
Crap, it's this late already!
Damn!
くそ
Somewhere...
どっか
どっかくらくねえとこ
Anywhere that isn't dark!
怖い
I'm scared.
It's dark.
暗いの
I'm scared.
怖いの
ママ　早く来て
Mommy... Please hurry...
うーちゃんのこと見てる
You're looking at me?
やばー
Shoot!
やっぱり
I knew it!
Everyone else ignores me for some reason!
あのね　皆無視するの
All these eyeball thingies
try to talk to me instead,
目玉お化けばっかしゃべってきて
but they're so scary!
なんか怖がって
こいつ
She's...
I'm waiting for my mommy's car.
うーちゃん　ママの車待ってるの
On the 23rd, a young girl
塾が終わったら
She comes to pick me up
after my lessons are over.
On the 23rd, a young girl
was
killed here
in a
hit-and-run
迎えに来るんだよ
was
killed here
in a
hit-and-run
Oh...
そう　なんだ
ねぇ　お兄ちゃん
Hey, stay with me until 6 o'clock.
六時まで一緒にいて
Until my mommy comes!
ママが来るまで
Sure.
いいよ
雪音君
Yukine-kun...
Sorry. Mommy's a little late.
ごめんね
ママちょっと遅れてるね
Your family must be worried about you too.
お兄ちゃんのお家の人も心配だよね
My family?
うち？
I don't really have one...
そんなの俺には
When my mommy gets here,
you should come with us, okay?
お兄ちゃん
ママが来たら　一緒に車乗ってって
She'll be here soon, okay?
だから
だから　もう少し　ねぇ
I... don't think she's coming.
多分こねえよ
Hey! Hold on!
おい　待てって
Yukine-kun!
雪音君　ここにいたんだ
Here you are!
Don't go over there!
そっちにゃ行くな
Huh?!
How terrible.
ひどいね
Poor little girl...
かわいそう　なこと　によ
Your mommy is over here.
君のママは こっちにいるよ
Really?
本当
Come this way.
おいで
Come here.
Yukine-kun!
雪音君
The thing Yato taught you!
夜トに教わったあれを
Put my fingers together like this...
指を矛にして
くそ
Damn!
...and draw a line!
一線
I'm sorry.
ごめんな　先は変なこと言って
I shouldn't have said that earlier.
It's okay now.
大丈夫
They can't cross that line.
あいつら　あの一線は越えらんねえから
Smells nice...
いい匂い
Smells nice... Smells nice...
Smells nice...
いい匂い
お兄ちゃん　いい匂いね
You...
smell really nice.
Smells nice...
いい匂い
Come...
You smell nice... Let me smell more...
いい匂い
もっと　頂戴
雪音君
Yukine-kun!
Give me... more...
お兄ちゃん　頂戴
Please...
More—
お兄ちゃん
Boy...
Mommy...
ママ
Yato!
夜ト
You okay, Yukine?!
雪音　大丈夫か
あやかしが　女の子が　中に
The Phantom...
A girl went into it...
Boy!
お兄ちゃん
あいつを 助けてやってくれよ
You have to help her!
Please!
頼む
分かった
All right.
Come, Sekki!
来い　雪器
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
豊葦原の中津国
荒び足らせぬ「彼」のものよ
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
我夜ト神来たり降り
雪器を以って砕きふせ
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
種々の障り穢れを打ち払わん
H-Hey!
おい
St...
や　やめろ
Stop!
Rend!
斬
What are you...
お前何やって
You're supposed to save her!
助けるんじゃないのかよ
この子はもう完全にあやかしに取りこまれちまってる
It's too late for that!
She's been completely possessed!
What are you talking about?!
何言って
Killing her's our only choice now!
もう斬るしかねえんだよ
Yukine...
雪音
あやかしに障られ　貪られた魂が行き着く先はな
A soul that's been corrupted and consumed by a Phantom
呪にまみれた生き地獄でしかねえんだ
will experience nothing but a living hell! Utter damnation!
だからこそ
That's why...
you need to free her!
あの子を解放してやれ
Yukine!
雪音
斬
Rend!
街を巡回中の囷巴（くらは）から報告が入りました
We've received word from Kuraha
who is presently patrolling the city.
「あやかしを斬る夜トを見かけた」と
He states he saw Yato slaying a Phantom.
新しい神器も手にしたようです
Yato appears to have obtained a new Regalia as well.
I see.
そうか
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
ki
mi
no
na
ma
e
na
ni
ga
a
tte
mo
ka
na
ra
zu
yo
bu
ka
ra
君の名前 何があっても
必ず呼ぶから
Your heart is all jagged
ki
mi
wa
gi
za
ha
a
to
no
mo
chi
nu
shi
君はぎざぎざハートの持ち主
So you hurt anything you touch
fu
re
ru
mo
no
wa
na
n
de
mo
ki
zu
tsu
ke
ru
触れるものは何でも傷つけ
Those eyes that frown at everything
se
ka
i
no
su
be
te
wo
ni
ra
mi
tsu
ke
te
世界のすべてを睨み付けて
その目は言うんだ
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
so
no
me
wa
i
un
da
bo
ku
wa
ko
ni
iru
「僕はここにいる」
Someone was laughing at you
da
re
ka
ga
wa
ra
tte
ta
誰かが笑ってた
だから引いたんだ その境界線
So you put that barrier around you
da
ka
ra
hi
i
tan
da
so
no
kyo
u
ka
i
sen
それなら
But I'll reach in there with my hand
so
re
na
ra
wa
ta
shi
ga
so
no
te
wo
hi
ku
私はその手を引く
さぁ
And bring you out
tsu
re
te
ku
ka
ra
連れてくから
言えないなら
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
i
e
na
i
ra
ko
no
te
wo
tsu
yo
ku
ni
gi
tte
この手を強く握って
And don't let go
ha
na
sa
i
de
離さないで
君はもう一人じゃないんだって
I want you to know that you
ki
mi
wa
mo
u
hi
to
ri
ja
na
i
n
da
tte
知ってほしいんだよ
Are not alone any more
shi
tte
ho
shi
in
da
yo
雪音君　お風呂よくあったたまった
Did you have a nice bath, Yukine-kun?
Yeah.
うん　ああ　シャンプー借りた
Oh, I used some shampoo.
なんかバラの香りのするやつ
The rose-scented kind or whatever.
Is that yours?
もしかして　あれってひよりの
お父様の育毛シャンプーだよ
That was my father's hair-growth shampoo.
おっさんの
That old guy's?!
On the next Noragami: "Scary Person."
Scary Person
Next Episode
次回　ノラガミ
コワイヒト